FRANCES **CONLEY-WOOD**

Full Stack Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

KidCuteTure, Graphic Designer & Web Management May 2015 - September 2015

- Updated all product inventories between multiple online platforms. Managed product details, generated new products per season, arranged sale/clearance items and removed out of stock inventory.
- Handled photo editing for the website and catalogue. During catalogue season I formatted dozens of images over one-week to meet a strict deadline, including all Photoshop touch-ups/edits.
- In charge of creating graphics for weekly e-mail blasts and social media.

Canoe, Private Dining Liaison May 2014 - Oct 2015, Toronto ON

- In-house liaison between the events department and our restaurant. Often handled 15-25 separate functions with dozens of updates and requests a day. All changes were approved directly by management, Chef or myself.
- Arranged Banquet Event Order packages for mangers attending our weekly meeting to introduce upcoming events and areas of foreseen difficulty. Surveyed open table reviews online, monitored menu packages and website updates to notify marketing of any issues.
- My job requirements adapted with the seasons. This could mean managing rotating staff during Summerlicious, receiving hundreds of phone reservations or jumping on the floor to assist with lunch service and staffing needs.

Grid & Mortar, Founder & Creative Director August 2013 - April 2015, Toronto ON

- With two partners I started a graphic design company, collaborating to identify our target market and develop a business plan. I handled all communication with clients and managed expectations.
- For each new project I developed project proposals and invoices. Over a three-month period I managed a project for Melbourne-based digital-democracy start-up OurSay, successfully designing a brand identity for a government funded voter engagement campaign.
- As creative director I oversaw projects and worked on separate graphic design jobs or researched as needed.

Luma, Private Dining Liaison October 2012 - May 2014, Toronto ON

- Took responsibility for organizing all events under 25 guests. I created Banquet Event Orders for my management team to ensure all functions ran smoothly and followed up with guests. During the Christmas season 2013 these additional in-house events brought in over \$20,000 in revenue.
- Had additional training to be a certified member of the Health and Safety Committee. Arranged monthly safety walkthroughs, updated staff safety board and attended monthly company wide meetings to resolve any foreseeable hazards in the restaurant.

f.conleywood@gmail.com







ABOUT

Hello! my name is Frances. I have an eye for design, a knack for building, and a passion for learning. My diverse work experiences along with my own interests have led me to web development as an ideal outlet for my creativity and entrepreneurial spirit. Web development (in all its glory) empowers me to express my creative vision in a socially relevant and ever expanding community.

EDUCATION

Web Development Bitmaker, Toronto ON 2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Major Studio Arts Concordia University, Montreal QC 2007 - 2011

SKILLS

Ruby on Rails Photoshop Illustrator Github Javascript HTML jQuery **CSS AJAX** SASS

Front-End

Back-End

AWARDS

Cossette Health Award, **Hacking Health Hamilton 2016**

(Title prize) Incubation, resources, programming and marketing/communications from Cossette Health.

Best Business Model, Hacking Health Hamilton 2016

Technical and business advisory services from Mohawk MEDIC.